[('Relational Database Management System', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('SQL', 'PERSON'), ('Structured Query Language', 'ORG'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bing', 'ORG'), ('7/1/2024', 'DATE'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Types, Features,', 'ORG'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('a Relational Database Management System', 'ORG'), ('3) Components', 'ORG'), ('Relational Database Management System', 'ORG'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('a Relational Database Management System', 'ORG'), ('Codecademy', 'PERSON'), ('https://www.codecademy.com/article/what-is-rdbms-sql', 'GPE'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('a Relational Database Management System', 'ORG')]