[('Quantum Data Wonderland', 'ORG'), ('Data Cloud Whirlwinds', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Mystical Symbols', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Whimsy Locators', 'PERSON'), ('Structured Query Language', 'ORG'), ('SQL', 'ORG'), ('BabelScript', 'PERSON'), ('Temporal Shapeshifts', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Quantum Data Wonderland', 'ORG'), ('Data Capers', 'ORG'), ('Data Resurrections', 'ORG'), ('Data Kaleidoscopes', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Quantum Data Wonderland', 'ORG')]