[('World War 3', 'EVENT'), ('World War III', 'EVENT'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Power Dynamics:*', 'ORG'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('the South China Sea', 'LOC'), ('Eastern Europe', 'LOC'), ('the Korean Peninsula', 'LOC'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Digital Warfare Challenges:*', 'ORG'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('10', 'CARDINAL')]