[('The Industrial Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('the Great Juggling Extravaganza', 'FAC'), ('Juggling Pavilions', 'ORG'), ('Acrobatic Inventions', 'LOC'), ('Circus Caravans', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Transportation', 'ORG'), ('Cannonball Catapults', 'ORG'), ('Clown Court', 'ORG'), ('juggler', 'PERSON'), ('the Industrial Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('juggler acrobat', 'PERSON')]