[('the French Revolution on European societies', 'EVENT'), ("The French Revolution's", 'EVENT'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('decades', 'DATE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Liberty, Equality,', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Shifting Political Landscape', 'ORG'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('the Napoleonic Wars', 'EVENT'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('decades', 'DATE'), ('Inspiration for Liberation Movements', 'ORG'), ('colonies', 'GPE'), ('Haiti', 'GPE'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('democratic', 'NORP'), ('European', 'NORP'), ("the French Revolution's", 'EVENT'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('today', 'DATE')]