[('the French Revolution on European societies', 'EVENT'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('the American revolution of', 'EVENT'), ('1776', 'DATE'), ('Empty', 'ORG'), ('the end of 1786', 'DATE'), ('Charles Alexandre de Calonne', 'PERSON'), ('centuries', 'DATE'), ('The King', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Estates', 'ORG'), ('Estates', 'ORG'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Estates', 'ORG'), ('1614', 'DATE'), ('May 5 1789', 'DATE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Difference Between Democracy and Monarchy', 'LAW'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('the late 18th century', 'DATE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Estates', 'ORG'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('State', 'ORG'), ('Louis XVI', 'PERSON'), ('State', 'ORG'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('the American War of Independence', 'EVENT'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Louis XVI', 'PERSON'), ('The 18th century', 'DATE'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('the ‘Divine Rights Theory', 'ORG'), ('Philosophers like Rousseau', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('i.e', 'NORP')]