[('the French Revolution on European societies', 'EVENT'), ('The French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Great Britain', 'GPE'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Austria', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Frenchmen', 'PRODUCT'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Royalists', 'NORP'), ('the French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('more than a century', 'DATE'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Napoleon', 'ORG'), ('Bourbon', 'PERSON'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('1814', 'DATE'), ('Frederick Artz', 'PERSON'), ('Italians', 'NORP'), ('the French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('nearly two decades', 'DATE'), ('Italians', 'NORP'), ('centuries', 'DATE'), ('Italians', 'NORP'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('the French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('Martin', 'PERSON'), ('Swiss', 'NORP'), ('Catholics', 'NORP'), ('Protestants', 'NORP'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Catholic Church', 'ORG'), ('Paris', 'GPE'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Revolution', 'EVENT')]