[('the French Revolution on European societies', 'EVENT'), ('The French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('German', 'NORP'), ('1790s', 'DATE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('German', 'NORP'), ('Paris', 'GPE'), ('Caroline Schlegel', 'PERSON'), ('Klopstock', 'ORG'), ('the French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('German', 'NORP'), ('Napoleon', 'ORG'), ('Francophobia', 'ORG'), ('German', 'NORP'), ('the early 19th century', 'DATE'), ('The French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('the Holy Roman Empire', 'FAC'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('1806', 'DATE'), ('Napoleonic', 'ORG'), ('Baden', 'GPE'), ('the years after 1815', 'DATE'), ('Greece', 'GPE'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Belgium', 'GPE'), ('Poland', 'GPE'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('German', 'NORP'), ('the Napoleonic years', 'DATE'), ('1815', 'DATE'), ('1847', 'DATE'), ('only four', 'CARDINAL'), ('39', 'CARDINAL'), ('the German Confederation', 'ORG'), ('Prussian', 'NORP'), ('Karl August', 'PERSON'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('1799', 'DATE'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Prussia', 'GPE'), ('Prussia', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('after 1848', 'DATE')]