[('the French Revolution on European societies', 'EVENT'), ('the French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('Napoleon', 'ORG'), ('1815', 'DATE'), ('many years', 'DATE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Measure', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('1795', 'DATE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('half', 'CARDINAL'), ('1789', 'DATE'), ('1789-1815', 'DATE'), ('The French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('the Estates General of 1789', 'ORG'), ("a 'National Assembly'", 'ORG'), ("a 'Declaration of the Rights of Man and the Citizen", 'LAW'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Napoleon', 'ORG'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('the 1800s', 'DATE'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('1815', 'DATE'), ('Napoleon', 'ORG'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('Europeans', 'NORP'), ('the nineteenth century', 'DATE'), ('the French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('Marianne', 'PERSON'), ('the French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('1830', 'DATE'), ('Delacroix', 'PERSON'), ('the 1830 Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('Matu', 'PRODUCT'), ('2020', 'DATE'), ('Liberty', 'GPE'), ('the Statue of Liberty', 'FAC'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('200 tonne', 'QUANTITY'), ('97', 'CARDINAL'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('100th', 'ORDINAL'), ('American', 'NORP')]