[('the French Revolution on European societies', 'EVENT'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('The French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Revolutionary', 'PERSON'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Bourbon', 'PERSON'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('400 years', 'DATE'), ('the French revolution', 'EVENT'), ('1792', 'DATE'), ('Republican', 'NORP'), ('Bourbon', 'PERSON'), ('Napoleon', 'ORG'), ('1830', 'DATE'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Jacobins', 'PERSON'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('175 years', 'DATE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Constitution and Rule of Law:', 'LAW'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Before 1789', 'DATE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('National Guard', 'ORG'), ('the National Guard', 'ORG'), ('Bourbon', 'PERSON'), ('National Guard', 'ORG'), ('the revolutionary army', 'ORG'), ('the French revolution', 'EVENT')]