[('the French Revolution on European societies', 'EVENT'), ('The French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('1789', 'DATE'), ('the 1790s', 'DATE'), ('Napoleon Bonaparte', 'ORG'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('the Near East', 'LOC'), ('1992', 'DATE'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('Watson', 'PERSON'), ('1992', 'DATE'), ('Secondly', 'ORDINAL'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('the Revolution for France,', 'EVENT'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Halliday, 1999', 'DATE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('the turn of the 18th\ncentury', 'DATE'), ('Louis XVI', 'PERSON'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('the American Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('Wendt, 1992', 'DATE'), ('decades', 'DATE'), ('Watson', 'PERSON'), ('1992', 'DATE'), ('French', 'NORP')]