[('the French Revolution on European societies', 'EVENT'), ('The French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('1789 to 1799', 'DATE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('The French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('The French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('between 1789 and 1799', 'DATE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Years', 'DATE'), ('the united states of America', 'GPE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Voltaire, Rousseau', 'LOC'), ('Montesquieu', 'ORG'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('the American Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('the American Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('the American Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Louis XVI', 'PERSON'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('Economic and Food Crises: In', 'ORG'), ('the years', 'DATE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('Estates', 'ORG'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('1789', 'DATE'), ('the National Assembly', 'ORG'), ('the French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('France', 'GPE')]