[('the French Revolution on European societies', 'EVENT'), ('The French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('1787 to 1799', 'DATE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('1789', 'DATE'), ('the “Revolution of 1789', 'EVENT'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('1830', 'DATE'), ('1848', 'DATE'), ('the end of the 18th century', 'DATE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('1789', 'DATE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('the American Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('1788', 'DATE'), ('the 17th and 18th centuries', 'DATE'), ('Philosophes', 'ORG'), ('Montesquieu', 'ORG'), ('Jean-Jacques Rousseau', 'PERSON'), ('France', 'GPE')]