[('the French Revolution on European societies', 'EVENT'), ('Scholars', 'PERSON'), ('the French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('1789 to 1799', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('democratic', 'NORP'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('the French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('the French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('the Ancien Régime', 'FAC'), ('June 1789', 'DATE'), ('Commons', 'ORG'), ('the National Assembly', 'ORG'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('The National Assembly', 'ORG'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('the Declaration of Rights', 'LAW'), ('France', 'GPE')]