[('the French Revolution on European societies', 'EVENT'), ("The French Revolution's", 'EVENT'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Human Rights and Enlightenment:', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('The Declaration of the Rights of Man', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Citizen', 'ORG'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ("The French Republic's", 'GPE'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('Napoleonic', 'ORG'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('The French Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('the Haitian Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Americas', 'LOC')]