[('Charles Darwin', 'PERSON'), ('The Origin of Species', 'ORG'), ('1859', 'DATE'), ('Darwin', 'PERSON'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Jean-Baptiste Lamarck', 'PERSON'), ('Alfred Russel Wallace', 'PERSON'), ('Darwin', 'PERSON'), ('Darwin', 'PERSON'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Wallace', 'PERSON'), ('Darwin', 'PERSON'), ('Darwin', 'PERSON'), ('the age of 50', 'DATE'), ('The Origin', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Wallace', 'PERSON'), ('502', 'CARDINAL'), ('Darwin', 'PERSON'), ('The Variation of Animals and Plants Under Domestication', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('1868', 'DATE'), ('The Descent of Man', 'ORG'), ('Selection in Relation', 'ORG'), ('The Expression of the Emotions in Man and Animals', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('1872', 'DATE'), ('Lamarck', 'PERSON'), ('Lamarckian', 'NORP'), ('CRISPR', 'PERSON'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lamarckian', 'NORP'), ('Lamarckian', 'NORP'), ('Lamarck', 'PERSON'), ('Darwinian', 'NORP'), ('Darwin', 'PERSON'), ('Lamarckian', 'NORP'), ('Darwin', 'PERSON'), ('Origin', 'PERSON'), ('Darwin', 'PERSON'), ('T. H. Huxley’s', 'GPE'), ('Theodosius Dobzhansky', 'PERSON'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mendelian', 'NORP'), ('the Modern Synthesis', 'ORG'), ('I. M. Lewis', 'PERSON'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lamarckian', 'NORP'), ('Darwinian', 'NORP'), ('Julian Huxley', 'PERSON'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Modern Synthesis', 'ORG'), ('1942', 'DATE'), ('the very next year', 'DATE'), ('Salvador Luria', 'PERSON'), ('Max Delbrück', 'PERSON'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Joshua', 'PERSON'), ('Esther Lederberg', 'PERSON'), ('6', 'CARDINAL')]