[('World War III', 'EVENT'), ('the Syrian Civil War', 'EVENT'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Libya', 'GPE'), ('Syria', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Palestine', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('World War III', 'EVENT'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('more than one', 'CARDINAL'), ('World War III', 'EVENT'), ('World War III', 'EVENT'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('World War III', 'EVENT')]