[('World War III', 'EVENT'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Territorial Disputes Ongoing', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the South China Sea', 'LOC'), ('Kashmir', 'LOC'), ('the Taiwan Strait', 'LOC'), ('Cyber Warfare Heightened', 'PERSON'), ('Ethnic', 'PRODUCT'), ('the Middle East', 'LOC'), ('South Asia', 'LOC'), ('Climate Change Environmental', 'ORG'), ('Global Health Crises Pandemics', 'ORG')]