[('Continental', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Alfred Wegener', 'PERSON'), ('the early 20th century', 'DATE'), ('Firstly', 'ORDINAL'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('Secondly', 'ORDINAL'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('the Appalachian Mountains', 'LOC'), ('North America', 'LOC'), ('the Caledonian Mountains', 'LOC'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Scandinavia', 'LOC'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE')]