[('continental', 'ORG'), ('Continental', 'ORG'), ('Alfred Wegener', 'PERSON'), ('1912', 'DATE'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Pangea', 'PRODUCT'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('Fossil', 'PERSON'), ('Mesosaurus', 'GPE'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('the Karoo Basin', 'LOC'), ('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Paleoclimate', 'ORG'), ('Antarctica', 'LOC'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('the 1960s', 'DATE'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ("Plates of Earth's", 'FAC'), ('Earth', 'LOC')]