[('Continental', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('Fossil', 'PERSON'), ('Antarctica', 'LOC'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Appalachian Mountains', 'LOC'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('poles', 'NORP'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC')]