[('continental', 'ORG'), ('Imagine Earth', 'FAC'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Fossil Frenzy', 'PERSON'), ('Glossopteris', 'PERSON'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Appalachians', 'NORP'), ('North America', 'LOC'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Paleoclimate', 'ORG'), ('Alfred Wegener', 'PERSON'), ('1912', 'DATE'), ('Pangea', 'ORG'), ('200 million years ago', 'DATE'), ('the 1960s', 'DATE'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Today', 'DATE'), ('continental', 'ORG')]