[('continental', 'ORG'), ('## Continental Drift', 'MONEY'), ('Continental', 'ORG'), ('millions of years', 'DATE'), ('Alfred Wegener', 'PERSON'), ('1912', 'DATE'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('Greek', 'NORP'), ('Over millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Madagascar', 'GPE'), ('Antarctica', 'LOC'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Mesosaurus', 'GPE'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('Glossopteris', 'PERSON'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Antarctica', 'LOC'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('Plate', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Continental', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('today', 'DATE')]