[('continental', 'ORG'), ('Continental Drift', 'ORG'), ('Continental', 'ORG'), ('the early 20th century', 'DATE'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('Fossil Distribution', 'PERSON'), ('Mesosaurus', 'GPE'), ('Glossopteris', 'PERSON'), ('Rock Formations', 'LOC'), ('the Appalachian Mountains', 'LOC'), ('North America', 'LOC'), ('the Caledonian Mountains', 'LOC'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Paleoclimate', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Limitations of Continental Drift', 'ORG'), ('the 1960s', 'DATE'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Continental', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Earth', 'LOC')]