[('continental', 'ORG'), ('Picture Earth', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Millions of years ago', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pangaea', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Earth', 'LOC')]