[('continental', 'ORG'), ('Continental', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Today', 'DATE'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('Alfred Wegener', 'PERSON'), ('the early 20th century', 'DATE'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Pangaea', 'GPE'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('Pangaea', 'ORG'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('only one meter', 'QUANTITY'), ('3.3 feet', 'QUANTITY'), ('the Atlantic Ocean', 'LOC'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('Arctic archipelago', 'LOC'), ('Svalbard', 'GPE'), ('Norway', 'GPE'), ('Arctic', 'LOC'), ('Svalbard', 'PERSON'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('the Appalachian Mountains', 'LOC'), ('United States', 'GPE'), ('the Caledonian Mountains', 'LOC'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Pangaea', 'GPE'), ('about 240 million years ago', 'DATE'), ('about 200 million years ago', 'DATE'), ('Over millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pangaea', 'PERSON'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Today', 'DATE'), ('Pangaea', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Pannotia', 'PERSON'), ('about 600 million years ago', 'DATE'), ('Rodinia', 'GPE'), ('more than a billion years ago', 'MONEY')]