[('the 16th century', 'DATE'), ('Abraham Ortelius', 'PERSON'), ("South America's", 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('western coast', 'LOC'), ('Alfred Wegener', 'PERSON'), ('1912', 'DATE'), ('Mesosaurus', 'PERSON'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('Appalachians', 'NORP'), ('North America', 'LOC'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('Pangaea', 'GPE'), ('200 million years ago', 'DATE'), ('Pangaea', 'PERSON'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('the 1960s', 'DATE'), ('Plate', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Continental', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC')]