[('continental', 'ORG'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('Alfred Wegener', 'PERSON'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('Pangaea', 'PERSON'), ('eons', 'DATE'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('the Appalachian Mountains', 'NORP'), ('North America', 'LOC'), ('the Caledonian Mountains', 'LOC'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Scandinavia', 'LOC'), ('Paleoclimatic', 'LOC'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('the mid-20th century', 'DATE'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC')]