[('continental', 'ORG'), ('Today', 'DATE'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('the early 20th century', 'DATE'), ('German', 'NORP'), ('Alfred Wegener', 'PERSON'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Continental Drift', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('years ago', 'DATE'), ('Pangaea', 'PERSON'), ('Pangaea', 'GPE'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('Theory of Continental Drift', 'ORG'), ('many years', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('First', 'ORDINAL'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Secondly', 'ORDINAL'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Theory of Continental Drift', 'ORG'), ('Mesosaurus', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('Lystrosaurus', 'PERSON'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Antarctica', 'LOC')]