[('continental', 'ORG'), ('Continental', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('German', 'NORP'), ('Alfred Wegener', 'PERSON'), ('the early 20th century', 'DATE'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('moved[1][2', 'ORG'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('the early 20th century', 'DATE'), ('the 1960s', 'DATE'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('history[3][5', 'PRODUCT')]