[('continental', 'ORG'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('Alfred Wegener', 'PERSON'), ('the early 20th century', 'DATE'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('Pangaea', 'ORG'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('Firstly', 'ORDINAL'), ('between the eastern boundary of South America', 'TIME'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('Secondly', 'ORDINAL'), ('the Appalachian Mountains', 'NORP'), ('North America', 'LOC'), ('the Caledonian Mountains', 'LOC'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Scandinavia', 'LOC'), ('Paleoclimatic', 'LOC'), ('Glacial', 'ORG'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('the mid-20th century', 'DATE'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC')]