[('Abraham Ortelius', 'PERSON'), ('the sixteenth century', 'DATE'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('Alfred Wegener', 'PERSON'), ('1912', 'DATE'), ('Mesosaurus', 'PERSON'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Appalachians', 'NORP'), ('North America', 'LOC'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('Pangaea', 'GPE'), ('200 million years ago', 'DATE')]