[('continental', 'ORG'), ('Billions of years ago', 'DATE'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pangea', 'PERSON'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('Fossil Family Reunion', 'PERSON'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('Magnetic Messages: Rocks', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Comparing', 'ORG'), ('Continental', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('today', 'DATE')]