[('continental', 'ORG'), ('Continental', 'ORG'), ('millions of years', 'DATE'), ('Alfred Wegener', 'PERSON'), ('1912', 'DATE'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('Fossil Matchups:*', 'PERSON'), ('Mesosaurus', 'GPE'), ('Glossopteris', 'PERSON'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rock Similarities:*', 'ORG'), ('the Appalachian Mountains', 'LOC'), ('North America', 'LOC'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ancient Climate Clues:** Glacial', 'ORG'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Continental', 'ORG'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Earth', 'LOC')]