[('continental', 'ORG'), ('Continental', 'ORG'), ('Alfred Wegener', 'PERSON'), ('1912', 'DATE'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Jigsaw Puzzle Fit:*', 'ORG'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('Fossil Distribution:*', 'PERSON'), ('Mesosaurus', 'PERSON'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rock Formations:*', 'ORG'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Glacial Evidence:*', 'ORG'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('Today', 'DATE'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC')]