[('Continental', 'ORG'), ('Alfred Wegener', 'PERSON'), ('the early 20th century', 'DATE'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Pangaea', 'ORG'), ('millions of years', 'DATE'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('Fossil', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mesosaurus', 'PERSON'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('the Appalachian Mountains', 'NORP'), ('North America', 'LOC'), ('the Caledonian Mountains', 'LOC'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Scandinavia', 'LOC'), ('Paleoclimatic', 'LOC'), ('Pangaea', 'GPE'), ('the east coast', 'LOC'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('continental', 'ORG')]