[('Quantum Data', 'ORG'), ('Data Cloud Whirlwinds', 'ORG'), ('Mystical Symbols', 'ORG'), ('Whimsy Locators', 'PERSON'), ('Structured Query Language SQL', 'ORG'), ('BabelScript', 'ORG'), ('Transactions', 'PERSON'), ('Shapeshifts', 'PERSON'), ('Quantum Data', 'ORG'), ('Data Capers', 'ORG'), ('Backup', 'PERSON'), ('Data Resurrections', 'ORG'), ('Normalization', 'ORG'), ('Data Kaleidoscopes', 'ORG'), ('Quantum Data', 'ORG')]