[('Data Mirage Generator', 'ORG'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Data Mirage Sandcastles', 'ORG'), ('Keys', 'PERSON'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('Cryptic Sigils', 'ORG'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Fata Morgana Beacons', 'PERSON'), ('fifth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Whimsical Query Poetry', 'ORG'), ('Transactions', 'PERSON'), ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Juggling Acts', 'ORG'), ('seventh', 'ORDINAL'), ('eighth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Data Mirage Dances', 'ORG'), ('Backup', 'PERSON'), ('ninth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Data Mirage Mirrors', 'ORG'), ('Normalization', 'LOC'), ('tenth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Data Mirage Mosaics', 'ORG'), ('mosaic', 'PRODUCT')]