[('Data Mirage Generator Rows', 'ORG'), ('Data Mirage Sandcastles', 'ORG'), ('Cryptic Sigils', 'ORG'), ('Indexes', 'PERSON'), ('Fata Morgana Beacons', 'PERSON'), ('Structured Query Language SQL', 'ORG'), ('Whimsical Query Poetry', 'ORG'), ('Transactions', 'PERSON'), ('Juggling Acts', 'ORG'), ('Data Mirage Dances', 'ORG'), ('Backup', 'PERSON'), ('Data Mirage Mirrors', 'ORG'), ('Data Mirage Mosaics', 'ORG')]