[('Quantum Data Flux Capacitor', 'ORG'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Data Nebulae', 'PERSON'), ('the Quantum Data Flux Capacitor', 'ORG'), ('Keys', 'PERSON'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('Mystical Symbols', 'ORG'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Whirlwind Portals', 'ORG'), ('Structured Query Language SQL', 'ORG'), ('fifth', 'ORDINAL'), ('BabelScript', 'GPE'), ('the Quantum Data Flux Capacitor', 'ORG'), ('Transactions', 'PERSON'), ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Temporal Fluxuations', 'ORG'), ('seventh', 'ORDINAL'), ('the Quantum Data Flux Capacitor Concurrency', 'ORG'), ('eighth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Backup', 'PERSON'), ('ninth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Data Phoenix Rituals', 'ORG'), ('tenth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Data Kaleidoscopes', 'ORG')]