[('Relational Database Management System', 'ORG'), ('the Data Wonderland', 'ORG'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Abstract Data', 'ORG'), ('Keys', 'PERSON'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('Enigmatic Lockets', 'ORG'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Whimsical Signposts', 'ORG'), ('Structured Query Language SQL', 'ORG'), ('fifth', 'ORDINAL'), ('ChaosSpeak', 'NORP'), ('Transactions', 'PERSON'), ('sixth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Random Rituals', 'ORG'), ('seventh', 'ORDINAL'), ('The Data Wonderland', 'ORG'), ('eighth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Chaotic Overlaps', 'ORG'), ('Backup', 'PERSON'), ('ninth', 'ORDINAL'), ('tenth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Data Anarchy This intentional chaos introduces', 'ORG')]