[('continental', 'ORG'), ('Alfred Wegener', 'PERSON'), ('the early century', 'DATE'), ('Pangaea', 'ORG'), ('Wegener', 'ORG'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('Fossil', 'PERSON'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('continental', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC')]